I thought I did okay my teammate told me
a lot that gave me a lot of confidence
this week and so did coach bag he
thought I was going to come out here and
play well I played pretty I played okay
Joe what about that affect development
maybe from one quarter in how much
comfortable more comfortable if you ask
me who's got that initial sort of the
hitter yeah I was a lot more comfortable
second quarter the series and I we got
going a little bit Antonio loans he
started run the ball pretty hard and are
often started clicking in the second
quarter it seemed like urban really gave
you a lot of praise in your development
throughout not only your whole time for
but specifically the spring did you feel
like you took a little step forward yeah
I put a little step forward but I still
a long way to go and I'm gonna work
really hard this summer to get where I
need to be to be the back of the Ohio
State okay what did you get out of this
spring is imola uh what I got out of it
was I know I can play here now and I
know what I need to do to get to be the
starting quarterback and what I need to
do to do the back of the season did you
doubt maybe last year if you can play
here I didn't but I think a lot of
people did and I think I showed that I
can't play here to all the coaching
staff and all the players on our team